mobileprice.pk 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy

Written by Administrator  Sunday, 10 May 2009 12:46 

Mobileprice believes that trust is an important component of the service we provide to our visitors and subscribers. To ensure that we earn and keep that trust, mobileprice makes every effort to protect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you about mobileprice's collection, use and disclosure of information you choose to share with us through the Site.

This Privacy Policy is considered to be a part of mobileprice's User Agreement. By using the Sites you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you are also consenting to mobileprice's privacy practices, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information that you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy.

We never rent, sell or share any information you give us. You privacy is important to us! When you visit the mobileprice site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes which pages are visited, types of form submitted, and any feedback from our visitors. We then collate this information with other pieces of information to improve our site and make your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible. Information are provided to authorized institutions only in case of legal requirement by the law of land.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**   
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.mobileprice.pk.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.mobileprice.pk and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense
